<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="it.baeyens.arduino.feature"
      label="Arduino Eclipse Extensions"
      version="3.0.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="Jan Baeyens">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      This feature allows easy creation of Arduino projects in an Eclipse
environment.
The main features are
a new arduino sketch wizard
a import library wizard
a button to build the project
a button to upload to the arduino board
a project property page allowing to change the arduino board
type and the port the arduino is using.
Version 2_1_4
Support for multiple configurations
Support for aternative soze command
Support for extentions to the C C++ compile instructions
Implementation of the eep compiler
Added flag to platform.txt to skip the archiver
New Arduino Icons
Support for Teensy 3
Hard coded Teensy uploaded comands are now using Platform.txt
Longer wait times for upload
Fix for due compilation
Version 2_0_0
New version for Arduino IDE 1.5.2 compatibility and without avr-eclipse
This version runs with Juno Only
Arduino project and sketch are in one eclipse project
Fixed problems with the indexer
Support for multiple boards.txt files added
Support for teensy added
Version 1_2_5
Cleaned up so that leonardo_test is not in the include path
Sorted the list of Arduino Boards
Version 1_2_4
Added Leonardo support
Undid the &quot;Fixed a bug on MAC when AVRPaths searches..)
Disabled searching for paths (other fix for the above undo)
Note 1_2_3 is not configurable on MAC.
Version 1_2_3
Added a serial test button to test the serial library in the
preference page
Fixed a bug to support non arduino cores (the correct include
folder is
now set)
Fixed a bug on MAC when AVRPaths searches for the location of
G++ AvrDude and others. (no MAC search as been added but the
POSIX is no longer used in case of mac)
Added suport for specific c compile, c++ compile and link instructions
the keys to be added to the boards.txt are
[board id].build.cpp.options
[board id].build.c.options
[board id].build.link.options
fixed the bug that when the &quot;private library&quot; is not selected
the eclipse environment is not setup properly. If not set a error
will pop up. it should not be possible to exit the preferences
without setting it.
Version 1_2_2
Added multiple library import
Added support for other cores than the Arduino (boards.txs file
attrribute XX.build.core)
Added serial monitor
version 1_2_1
Changed the lib for MAC os to a 4 architecture lib.
version 1_2_0
Added Com functionality.
Available Com ports are listed where you can select a com port
Now all arduino boards are reset when doing an upload.
adde , to the list of non allowed characters
version 1_1_6
Some board names contain ( and ) which gives problems when creating
the arduino project names.
This has been fixed now.
When importing a library the selected project is used as the
default project.
Error handling during import pops up now
Version 1_1_5
Mac os is supported now. This means the errors have been removed
and the default values should be ok.
Version 1_1_3
Fixes a bug that the latest used com port is used to uload a
file to arduino. Now the correct set port is used.
version 1_1_2
The ARDUINO define is now built based on the version.txt file.
The in eclipse define has been removed.
version 1_1_1 
includes better error reporting (now errors are also shown in
a dialog box and not only logged in the error log.
Bixes a bug when that made the referenced project corrupt when
changing the arduino board.
version 1_1_0 is a major change.
It fixed the incompatibilities with arduino 1.0
Therfore the arduino core library is replaced by arduino board
library (ths was needed due to the pins_arduino
I ow use the programmer as described in boards.txt
version 1_0_9 fixed unix incompatibilities
version 1_0_8 fixed the ok button not enabled in preference page
version 1_0_7 changed licence agreement and fixes issues 
import of arduino library subforder &quot;utilities&quot;
the c perspective is now proposed when a new project is created.
version 1_0_6 add import library functionality
previous versions are no longer available
This is a plugin build upon the avr-eclise plugin.
I included the avr-eclipse source code in this feature because
I had to make some changes and didn&apos;t want to wait for the next
version of the avr-eclipse plugin.
To avoid conflict I had to rename de .innot to it.baeyens. I
kept the same ID to keep the plugins data compatible.
Jan
   </description>

   <copyright>
      All rights reserved by the owning parties.
Arduino-&gt;       Copyright (c) 2011 Jan Baeyens
Remaining code of AVR-eclipse
AVR-eclipse-&gt;  Copyright (c) 2008, 2010 Thomas Holland (thomas@innot.de)
Boards code
Trump211
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.eclipse.org/org/documents/epl-v10.html">
      This software is licensed under GPL Version 3.0
This software sends non personalised activity data (build/upload/open serial monitor/open scope) to baeyens.it for statistical analyses of the usage of the plugin.
If you do not agree with this policy, then please do not install this software.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Arduino eclipse plugin V2 update site" url="http://www.baeyens.it/eclipse/V2/"/>
      <discovery label="AVR-Eclipse offers plenty of godies for AVR development" url="http://avr-eclipse.sourceforge.net/wiki/index.php/Plugin_Download"/>
      <discovery label="jan&apos;s site with plenty of documentation" url="http://www.baeyens.it/eclipse/"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import feature="org.eclipse.cdt" version="8.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="it.baeyens.arduino.common"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="it.baeyens.arduino.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="it.baeyens.arduino.monitor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="it.baeyens.arduino.core.nl1"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.0.0.qualifier"
         fragment="true"/>

   <plugin
         id="it.baeyens.arduino.application"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="it.baeyens.cdt.refactor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
